[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
From this day forward,
you will address me by my real name.
Lily Cruz.
[Robert] This is not your arena
anymore, Governor.
Mateo Ruiz is officially the governor now.
Don't lose yourself
in fighting a lost game
or else it'll be harder for you
to restore your name.
[Lily] Diego and I will be the bridges
connecting you to the new government.
[Emilia] Even though we're
no longer in power,
I can still make your life miserable.
Just accept that both you
and your family have lost.
What's more important to you?
Becoming the queen of Ardiente,
or discovering your mom's identity?
Both. I want to be the queen of Ardiente
and have acting governor Mateo Ruiz
at my beck and call.
-Someone wants to see you.
-Who?
Red Dragon.
I am now the consultant
of Governor Mateo Ruiz.
I will help him with decisions
that affect this town.
Governor, is this a joke?!
Whether you like it or not,
I get to decide for the governor.
[Mercedes] Madam, here's
the research you ordered.
Governor, could you give me a second?
Next time, talk to my secretary
if you want an appointment.
Oh, I'm sorry about that, Governor.
I thought that, being your consultant,
I could go straight to you.
And I thought also that, you know,
we should work closely together
for the people of Ardiente.
Okay, fine. What is it? Make it quick.
I'm in a hurry, okay?
[exhales] So, you really do
like it fast, huh?
Don't waste my time.
Okay.
First off, I'd like to thank you
for appointing me
as your consultant.
Can I call you "Mateo"?
Since it's just the two of us
here right now.
Tell me the truth.
Does my father have anything
to do with your decision?
No.
Hmm…
Then, who?
You know, I'm just wondering.
Because, if I remember it correctly,
you rejected me before,
even if I offered you
something more than
what your wife could give you.
Emilia, I chose you because I like you.
In fact, I've been eyeing you
for a long time.
But you're an Ardiente, and I'm a Ruiz.
World War III will erupt
if we mess around.
But, who knows?
Behind closed doors, maybe we
could work something out?
Careful, Mateo. Don't mix
business with pleasure.
We're both married.
So, don't give in to temptation.
Excuse me.
[unsettling music playing]
[sighs]
I heard Emilia's happy
with her new position.
She reminds me of you, madam.
Hungry for power.
And like you, Emilia could have it all.
[suspenseful music playing]
Hi, Papa.
Hmm.
Hello there.
My daughter, please, please.
You look a little tired.
How was your first day at work?
Um, tiring, Papa.
Uh… Have you had dinner already?
Yeah, I'm good.
Would you like a piece
of cake or ice cream?
No, thanks, Papa.
But I think you need
something from me. What is it?
Oh, come on. Isn't that a little too much?
Haven't you gotten used
to our love-hate relationship?
We will always have our petty quarrels.
But, where the rubber hits the road,
we will be there for each other.
At the end of the day, my dear,
we will always be family.
I know, Papa.
I just can't believe you're
being so nice to me right now.
-So, what do you need?
-No… Actually…
Actually, I just have this
very little favor to ask of you.
I knew you needed something.
Okay, what is it?
-Look, it's a very small favor.
-I knew it.
Now that you're working
for this Mateo Ruiz…
-[Emilia] Yes?
-[Julio] I want you to sabotage
all of his projects, lead him to his ruin.
That way, I can become governor again.
Seriously, Papa?
Aren't you still under trial?
You know what? Instead of
serving at the capitol,
you'll end up serving time in prison.
[Julio] Come on, Emilia.
How many times have cases like
these been filed against me?
Have you ever seen me
spend a day in prison?
I've never been imprisoned,
and the day will never come
that I will be.
Just make sure that by the end
of my 90-day suspension,
Mateo Ruiz will have been
kicked out of my office.
-I'll think about it, Papa.
-What?!
Think about--
Emilia, this is your obligation!
It's your obligation to this family
to make sure that we will remain in power!
And what is it
that you want me to do, Papa?
It's very simple.
You're the only one who can do this
because you're the only woman among us.
You're a woman. And he's a man.
You're a very attractive woman.
I'm sure he'll give in to you.
Papa! You're going to use me
as a prostitute?
No way! I'm not doing it!
Emilia, you don't have to go that far.
Men are like dogs.
[imitates dog barking]
A few pats on the head,
a little caress here and there,
and they're all yours.
We all have sacrifices
to make for this family.
-I know.
-[Julio] Good. You see?
I knew you'd understand
and you'd get the point.
Goodbye, Mr. Mateo Ruiz.
[Julio chuckles]
I'm sure it wasn't an Ardiente
who influenced Governor Ruiz
because they don't have any power left.
They only have their name to hold on to.
The Ruiz I know isn't like that.
He's not afraid of any Ardiente.
The Ardientes are his enemies.
There's no way he'd form
an alliance with them.
But then, we all know how politics works.
Your enemy today
could be your ally tomorrow.
[scoffs]
What if he just wanted to be governor
so he could fulfill
his own personal ambitions?
[Diego] If that's the case,
we shouldn't have trusted him so easily.
Diego, it's not our fault.
We needed Governor Ruiz to take
Julio down, and we succeeded.
But we still have to face the facts.
The world never runs out of evil people.
And soon enough we'll find out
who's manipulating Governor Ruiz.
One thing's for sure,
it's not an Ardiente.
I'm sure of it.
Raul, you're here.
[scoffs]
Did I hear that right?
Huh?
You're working for that fool?
Fool? Who?
Isn't it obvious?
Who else are you working for?
I'm talking about the governor.
-Is it true?
-Here we go…
What's your connection with him?
Why did he hire you
as his consultant? What's going on?
Raul, what's up with you?
I'm tired. I want to rest.
Wait. I'm not done talking to you.
I'm asking you. What's going on? Tell me!
What's there for me to tell you?
Did something happen between you?
I can't believe you and Papa
think the same thing about me!
He hired me as his consultant
because I am the former governor
and mayor of this town,
which means I can help him.
If he has a hidden agenda,
-that's not my problem anymore!
-Yes, it is!
That should be your concern
because we're married!
Unless you're doing all this
on purpose just to mess with me!
Just because I let that thing between you
-and the Jaguar slide…
-What?
Now, you've got another guy lined up?
And you even chose that Mateo!
Am I nothing to you?!
You checked my phone, didn't you?
I'm changing my password right now!
See? If you aren't guilty,
you wouldn't do that!
You know what, Raul? We are nothing alike.
You give in to any woman
who so much as smiles at you.
Now you know how painful it was
for me every time you cheated!
Now, you know how it feels,
so deal with it!
[footsteps fading]
[sighs]
Hmm…
[chuckles]
Oh, Emilia. It's hard being beautiful.
Today marks the beginning
of the fulfillment of my dreams.
Ever since I was a kid,
I've been longing
for a prosperous Ardiente.
That was also my father's dream
before he passed away.
This will be the site
for the media complex,
which will provide education and jobs
to all the citizens of Ardiente.
[applause]
[suspenseful music playing]
Stop!
What are you doing here?
I have an order from the office
of the governor
to stop this event because
you're lacking some permits.
Also, you didn't get my approval.
I highly doubt that, Emilia.
This isn't illegal!
We have the necessary permits,
so you can't stop me
from fulfilling my plans!
And which city official did you
sleep with to earn your permit?
Well, Emilia, I'm not like you.
We went through due process.
I have a cease and desist order
from the office of the governor.
I don't care about that.
We didn't ask your office for funds.
Just so you know, this project
is 100% funded by Aguas Realty.
Furthermore, I bought this space.
And that means you're trespassing!
But you have to stop
this little project of yours, Lily Cruz,
until we settle this dispute in court.
Do you have a title?
I do. Want me to slap it in your face?
Well, I also have a title
to slap your face with!
-Go ahead!
-Huh?
Don't test me, Emilia.
That is fake.
Yours is the fake one! Just like you!
In case you didn't hear me right…
You need to leave!
You have to get out of here!
Just to repeat myself!
I bought this space!
Therefore, you're trespassing! Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Did you hear me?
Just try and come back here, Emilia.
I'll make sure you'll go deaf!
Get out!
-That's right!
-Serves them right.
Sorry about that.
I just don't want anyone
maltreating any of you
because this project is
for everyone's benefit.
-[applause]
-Thank you.
Just call me tomorrow,
or visit me in my office
at around 4:00 p.m.
-Mateo Ruiz.
-Thank you.
-Hold on. Sir, wait.
I just need to talk to him.
Let me speak with him.
-Let me talk to him.
-It's fine. Let him talk.
What is it?
What are you doing with my wife? Huh?
Why did you hire her as your consultant?
You're planning to do something
with her, aren't you?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
You know exactly what I'm talking about!
-You're making a pass at my wife!
-Sir, calm down.
You know who I am.
You know what I'm capable of doing!
You've got a lot of nerve!
Tell me. What can you possibly do to me?
You're no longer the Raul Torillo
that people feared.
No one respects you anymore.
Even your wife mocks you because
you're nothing but a loser!
Loser, huh?
[suspenseful music playing]
Attorney, I can't let
Emilia delay this project.
This is for the townspeople.
The people will lose
if we let this happen.
Her papers are fabricated.
But nonetheless, she can cause problems
and delay the project
with her dirty tactics.
That's Emilia's plan.
Even if we win in court,
she'll be more than happy
if she can obstruct us.
No. We won't let it reach court.
Attorney, what we're going to do
is start a signature campaign
to show the government
the amount of support
this project is receiving.
That way, they'll stop Emilia.
This project is for the townspeople,
so we'll let their voices be heard.
What signature campaign, Papa?
That is what I heard.
And if they get enough support,
Mateo will be forced to favor them.
You can't let this happen, Emilia.
You have to do something about it.
-Miss Loring. How's it going?
-[Loring] Yes?
-Have you gathered many signatures?
-Distribute this to everyone.
-I think this is enough.
-Here. Take these.
But we have more areas
-to go to.
-Make everyone sign.
-[Loring] Mm-hmm.
-Remember, everyone,
we need one million signatures.
We'll pass this to the local government
to let them know how important
Lily Cruz's project is to us.
We won't lose to the Ardientes.
You know very well,
just as the Ardientes do,
that we can take them on! Right?
-That's right!
-Right!
You heard her, everyone.
Don't give up! Fight!
[townspeople] Fight!
They were able to gather more
than a million signatures
in less than a week.
Their campaign was very effective.
They even went viral.
Governor Ruiz was forced
to let the project happen.
Madam, Lily Cruz has the people
of Ardiente behind her.
It's about time we let her know
that you're not to be messed with.
[suspenseful music playing]
[tires screeching]
Who are you? What do you want?
[suspenseful music playing]
[men grunting]
[men groaning, grunting]
[suspenseful music playing]
Jaguar? What is this?
[in distorted voice] Emilia Ardiente.
I just want you to know that she's mine.
I don't care about Emilia.
She's all yours.
[in distorted voice]
You better make sure of that.
Because if you're lying,
I'll come for you.
[Mateo groans]
[suspenseful music playing]
[sensual music playing]
Ma'am, hold on.
Jepoy?
Anna.
It's okay. Just wait for me outside.
Why are you here?
You didn't tell me you were coming.
It's late, and it's dangerous outside.
I'll drop you home.
It's okay. Lily gave me
bodyguards, remember?
Anna, you actually trust them
more than me?
[soft tense music playing]
-[line ringing]
-[phone ringing]
Yes, I trust them
because I'm the only one they're guarding.
-While you--
-Anna.
[sets phone down]
Anna, wait. Anna.
[romantic music playing]
Listen.
Why don't you tell
your bodyguards to go for now?
I'll be your bodyguard tonight.
[romantic music playing]
It's all right, Jepoy. Maybe next time.
You should go to her.
Don't keep a lady waiting.
Anna… Anna.
Mateo, I thought we already
decided to reject
whatever project Lily Cruz starts up!
Why did you approve of her project?!
Lily got the people's support.
Also, it called the attention
of the media.
If we rejected the project,
it'll be held against us.
So what? Emilia Ardiente is your backer.
That should be enough reason
for you to stand your ground
against Lily Cruz!
Emilia, I've made my decision,
and my decision is final, okay?
So, stop with the bickering!
No! This isn't over!
You think I don't notice
you disregarding me?
You wouldn't want to mess with me, Mateo.
[Mateo] I just don't want
any issues, Emilia.
You know, ever since you started
working for me,
I've had so many rivals.
So, if you want this partnership
to last, tell off your allies.
My allies? Who are you talking about?
Why don't you ask Jaguar?
To Aguas Realty. Cheers!
Cheers!
[Paterno] Congratulations.
Lily.
-Mr. Paterno.
-Congratulations.
Your dream project
is finally in the works.
Thank you. How was Europe?
Uh… Melissa and I?
Yeah, we had a great time in Europe.
Well, please send my regards to your wife.
Of course.
And, Mr. Paterno, thank you very much
for helping and supporting
my little pet project.
Uh, you know what?
As long as it doesn't affect
our business negatively…
I'm all for your charitable
endeavors. Count on it.
Thank you.
Well, Mr. Paterno, our company
is blessed with so much success.
So, it's our duty
to give back to the community.
-All right.
-Again, thank you.
And congratulations.
-[glasses clinking]
-Thank you.
[tense music playing]
Jaguar!
You know, I hate you! I really hate you!
[in distorted voice] Leave us for now.
Yes, boss.
Why did you do that, huh?!
Why did you attack Mateo?
Are you trying to ruin my plans?!
What's up with you, Emilia?
What's up with me, huh?
You're ruining my plans
for Governor Mateo Ruiz!
So, why did you attack him?
I just don't want you
getting close to that man.
I knew it all along!
You're so heartless, you know that?
All you want is power, money,
and control over Ardiente.
But, you don't care about me. I knew it!
That's enough, Emilia!
I don't want you getting any close to him.
Because I'm jealous.
I think you better leave.
[chuckles]
So, Jaguar's in love with me now?
[mellow music playing]
[water running]
Should I give this to her?
Are they sweet enough?
What if she gets the wrong message?
What if she thinks I'm courting her?
No, what if I get turned down?
Damian!
The food's almost ready.
We'll be eating in a bit.
All right.
What's that?
-That thing you're holding.
-Uh… This?
Um… They're mangoes.
I can't finish them all.
I picked them earlier.
Um… Do you want some?
Oh, sorry, Damian!
I was at the market earlier,
and I already bought mangoes.
Is that so?
No worries. I'll just give these
to someone else, okay?
No, wait!
Let me have them.
Really?
Yeah, let's just give mine away, instead.
[chuckles]
Thank you, Damian.
-Check them out.
-Okay.
-Look. See how ripe they are?
-They are.
They're really sweet.
Thanks.
Whether it's against Ivy Aguas
or Lily Cruz, you still lost!
What's the point of becoming
that vile vermin's consultant
if you can't even influence
any of his decisions?!
You're useless!
Ma'am, sir! It's Mr. Arnaldo.
Why? What happened to my grandson?
Please, come upstairs
and see for yourself.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Julio] Arnaldo?
-Arnaldo?
Arnaldo?
Amen.
[dramatic music playing]
Uh…
Who are you?
[tense music playing]
[line ringing]
Anna.
Anna, I'm here outside.
I was hoping we could go
see Lily together.
Are you sure you don't have other plans?
Yeah, I'm sure of it.
I know it's a special day
for you and Lily,
so I figured
I could be your bodyguard today.
Just to make it up to you.
All right. I'm on my way out.
Okay. I'll wait.
[suspenseful music playing]
Come with us.
What--Wait!
Go ahead and try!
-[grunts]
-[crackling sound]
[goon] Let's go!
[goon 2] Hurry up!
[suspenseful music playing]
Lily, I'll just be with Loring, okay?
-Sure, Mom.
-Excuse me.
-Okay.
Okay.
This building's construction
was halted due to lack of funds,
but since Aguas Realty owns this now,
the media complex for the
residents of Poblacion, Ardiente
can now be erected.
Your help made all this possible.
So thank you very much.
Um…
[suspenseful music playing]
Mr. Paterno, let's go?
You take the lead so we can
begin the building inspection.
[suspenseful music playing]
-Good day, ma'am.
-Good day.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Lily] And the--
Um… Miss?
[suspenseful music playing]
Diego, do you know that woman?
Doesn't she work here?
I think so. But all alone?
Diego, please gather everyone outside.
All right.
[suspenseful music playing]
Mister, have you seen Jepoy?
No, ma'am.
Hold on. Let me go and check.
Never mind. We're running late
for Lily's event.
[bodyguard] All right.
[suspenseful music playing]
Watch your step.
Uh, Diego, have you seen
my mom and Miss Loring?
Uh, they're inside.
Oh, there they are.
[Lily] Okay, good.
Okay. I think um… that's it for today.
[beeping sound]
[explosions]
[screaming]
Ivy.
[Diego] Auntie? Auntie.
[Ivy] Mom! Mom!
-[Diego] Auntie.
-Mom.
[groans] Uncle.
[whimpering]
[suspenseful music playing]
Mom, I think you should go home now.
Go home, and call Anna and Jepoy.
Check on them, and let me know
if they're okay. Okay?
-Go! Get the car ready!
-What about you, Lily?
Come with me. This place isn't safe.
I'm sorry, Mom, but I can't
leave my employees here.
Uncle, you go ahead. We'll catch up.
-Come with us!
-Auntie.
-Get moving! Come on!
-[Diego] Go, Uncle.
-Go ahead. We'll be fine.
-Get the car ready!
Go, Auntie. I'll take care of Lily.
-Please. Go, Nanny, Uncle.
-Mom, I'll call you.
[Loring] Why don't you just come with us?
Mr. Paterno, are you okay?
Please, call an ambulance.
Hurry! Check if everyone's okay!
-[line ringing]
-Hello?
-[tense music playing]
-[fire crackling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[reporter] Six condominium buildings
were simultaneously bombed today,
as well as a media complex
being constructed
under Aguas Realty.
All the buildings are notably
owned by Lily Cruz,
formerly known as Ivy Aguas.
Terrorists are thought
to be behind the bombings.
Stay tuned for news updates.
[suspenseful music playing]
Six condominium buildings
and a media complex
owned by Aguas Realty
were bombed earlier this morning
in what could be
the deadliest terrorist attack
in recent memory.
Please stay tuned for more updates…
It's clear you were the target
of those bombings.
Who could've done this? Who?
Did you receive the money?
-Yes, ma'am.
-[Mercedes] Good.
That is our thank-you gift
for your successful mission.
[suspenseful music playing]
Wait… What's… Hey! Stop!
I said stop! Where am I?!
-She's here. Let's go.
-Who's here?
Hey! Where am I?
Where are you going?
Let me go! I'm talking to you!
[grunts]
Well, hello, Madrigal.
Ma'am? Ma'am, what's going on?!
Well, what Natalie wants, Natalie gets.
You didn't have to do this, ma'am.
Three men had to bring me here.
-I'm sorry.
-They even tasered me.
Oh. I'm sorry about that.
But I finally have you where I want you.
So, are you going to
make this harder for me?
-Mm?
-Ma'am…
Ma'am, wait.
Ma'am…
[grunts]
We are facing dozens of lawsuits.
We'll have to cover the medical expenses,
as well as compensation for the injured!
Take note, we'll spend millions
just to pay for freaking damages!
The company might lose billions.
That's it.
Aguas Realty is done for,
and it's all your fault.
With all the enemies you've made,
they're after us now.
[tense music playing]
Yes.
This is my fault.
But as the CEO of this company,
I promise you, while I'm here,
Aguas Realty will not go under.
What we need to do now
is to help each other.
And we need to help all the victims.
[tense music playing]
Arnaldo is suffering
from retrograde amnesia.
It has a chance of occurring in patients
who woke up from a coma,
coming from a catatonic state.
Let's give him time.
Eventually, he will regain
all his old memories.
Arnaldo.
Do you remember me?
I'm your grandfather.
I was the one who raised and molded you…
to be the mayor of this town.
[Emilia] Yes, Arnaldo.
You were the mayor before.
You were supposed to run for governor,
but you fell into a coma.
[Julio] You are an Ardiente, Arnaldo.
The Ardiente family is the wealthiest…
and most powerful clan in this province.
Truth is, this place
was even named after us.
And you…
You are the heir to my throne.
Arnaldo, I'm your mother.
And I'm your father, Arnaldo.
Grandpa.
-Mom.
-Mm-hmm.
Dad.
So, do you remember us now?
Not really.
But… But I want to thank you all.
Because, since I've been
unstable and unconscious
for so long…
I can only imagine how long
you suffered and waited.
So, thank you very much
for not leaving me.
May I ask what happened to me?
You were shot in the head.
I was shot in the head? How…
Yes. We'll tell you the story,
but not now.
-Right.
-In bits and pieces.
So you won't be shocked.
Yes. You better get some rest for now.
Did someone really shoot me?
Do I have enemies?
Arnaldo, I think, for now,
we should just be thankful
that you're finally awake.
Uh…
We can now carry on with
the plans we've made together.
All right. Again, thank you very much.
[exhales]
Please bless my family. Guide them always.
What did he say?
This I pray always. Forever.
I think the boy is just tired.
We should give him some time to rest.
Doc, please let him rest for now.
[indistinct chatter]
[Arnaldo] Thank you.
Based on our investigations,
Aguas Realty did not fall short
in our security measures
within any of our establishments.
This series of bombings were a deliberate
and deadly act of terrorism
to hurt, kill, and instill fear.
They may have destroyed our buildings,
but never our spirit.
They've only made Aguas Realty stronger.
We will rise again,
and we will be a symbol
of strength, courage, and hope.
We will help all of the victims,
and we will hunt down
whoever was behind this.
This is an attack on justice, freedom,
and the future of our country.
That is why, I, Lily Cruz,
and Aguas Realty, humbly ask
for your help and support.
We need to show them…
that we are not afraid,
and we will not let them bring us down
because we're all united
in this fight.
[applause]
This is fantastic! Just great, you know?
Whoever is behind these bombings
is giving Lily Cruz victory
on a silver platter!
They're only boosting
that woman's resolve!
Really, Papa?
You're not the one responsible
for those bombings?
I wasn't! Because if I'm going
to blow something up,
I won't waste my time
with those buildings.
I'd blow up Lily Cruz's head!
Hold on, Papa. If you're not
the one behind that, then who?
Does this mean Lily Cruz has a new enemy?
Ma'am, we can still fix this,
but we're going to get delayed
with the schedule.
We need extra manpower to speed things up.
All right. Let's hire a few more workers.
This area here was
-[Diego] Lily.
-the most damaged.
The townspeople are here,
and they're all ready to help.
Good! Because investors
are committing 10 billion pesos
for the rehabilitation of Aguas Realty,
and they're offering to shoulder
some of the victims' medical expenses.
Lily, you have everyone's
full trust and support.
You're not alone in this fight, Miss Lily.
We're right behind you! Right?
-Yeah!
-We're with you.
-Thank you, everyone.
-Excuse me. Move aside.
Poor people, move, I need space.
Excuse me.
-There she goes again.
-Excuse me.
Hi, Lily Cruz.
The Governor's office sent me here
to show our support for your project.
So, how are you, Lily?
Well, what can I say?
That was one "explosive" surprise.
You shook the whole world!
Don't tell me the Ardientes
didn't have anything
to do with those bombings.
Excuse me, Camia. Watch your mouth.
We don't know anything about that.
In fact, I went here to know.
I want to know who's responsible
for those bombings,
so I can hug him or her,
and then shake their hand,
and tell them, "Good job!"
Well, this little guy
wants to know you better.
Aren't you going to leave?
Did that bother you?
Why are you so worked up about this?
-Aren't you going to leave?!
-I'm going!
-Get out of here!
-I'm leaving!
-[man] Leave!
-Get out!
[exasperated sigh]
I don't believe the Ardientes
weren't involved!
Emilia was just lying again.
I'm sorry, Mom, but it's possible
that she was telling the truth.
The Ardientes have been crippled.
They're incapable of carrying out
simultaneous bombings.
So, if they aren't behind it, who is?
Who else could possibly go against you?
My thoughts exactly.
The Ardientes are my only enemies.
But I suspect that someone
is helping them.
Someone who is capable
of a large-scale terror attack.
I'll find out who they are.
Are you all right?
Diego, do you remember that woman
at the construction site?
The one I asked you about?
Yes. Why?
I didn't tell you earlier,
but I have a strong feeling
that she may have something
to do with the bombings.
Why didn't you tell that
to the investigator?
We don't know who we're up against.
At this point, we shouldn't trust anyone.
So, I hope we can keep this conversation
between the two of us for now.
What's important now is
for me to find that woman.
I believe she's our key to finding out
who's behind the bombings.
[suspenseful music playing]
Has our investment
in Aguas Realty been approved?
They have to go through me.
[Paterno] That Lily Cruz
is so full of herself!
Blow them up.
[Mr. Paterno] I would like you to meet
Mrs. Mercedes' associate.
You! Stop her!
[people clamoring]
[reporter] We're here at the
main office of Aguas Realty
where an alleged
terrorist threat was reported.
Looks like karma is a bigger witch
than you are, Miss Lily Cruz.
Where's the bomb?!
[suspenseful music playing]
[theme music playing]